Show the universe who you truly are.
Troop Zero is a comedy, drama, family film directed by Bertie.
In rural 1977 Georgia, a misfit girl dreams of life in outer space.
When a national competition offers her a chance at her dream, to be recorded on NASA’s Golden Record, she
recruits a makeshift troupe of Birdie Scouts, forging friendships that last a lifetime and beyond.
Christmas Flint, played by Mckenna Grace.
Miss Rayleen, played by Viola Davis.
Ramsey Flint, played by Jim Gaffigan.
Miss Massey, played by Allison Janney.
Joseph, played by Charlie Shotwell.
Hell-No Price, played by Milan Ray.
Troop Zero is a 2019 American comedy-drama film directed by Bert & Bertie (Amber Templemore-Finlayson and Katie Ellwood), from
a screenplay by Lucy Alibar and inspired by Alibar's 2010 play Christmas and Jubilee Behold The Meteor Shower.
The film stars Viola Davis, Mckenna Grace, Jim Gaffigan, Mike
Epps, Charlie Shotwell, and Allison Janney.
Troop Zero had its world premiere as the closing film of Sundance Film Festival on February 1,
2019, and was released in the United States by Amazon Studios on January 17, 2020.
The film was met with mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of friendship, nasa, georgia,
based on play or musical, elementary school.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.